0412 420834 Tashi no koi (My rainy days) (Romance | Drama)
0412 420834 My Rainy Days (天使の恋 Tenshi no Koi, lit: Angel's Love) is a 2009 Japanese romance drama film based on the popular cell phone novel of the same name. Seventeen year old high school student Rio Ozawa is always the center of attention due to her beauty. Yet Rio has never cared about anyone but herself due to her traumatic past. But when she meets 35-year-old college professor Kouki Ozawa, and falls in love for the first time. She changes from a confident, mature person, to something more like a typical schoolgirl with a huge crush.

0612 104234 Beauty inside (fantasy | romance)
0612 104234 Beauty inside is a 2015 star-studded South Korean high-concept romantic comedy film based on the 2012 American social film The Beauty Inside, about a man who wakes up every day in a different body.
0612 104234 Furniture designer Woo-jin wakes up in a different body every day, regardless of age, gender and nationality. Sometimes he's a man, a woman, old, young, or even a foreigner. He's the same person on the inside, but on the outside he's always someone new. Looking at a different face in the mirror every morning is hard for him to get used to.

0312 043334 3 Idiots (Comedy | Youth)
0312 043334 The film follows the friendship of three students at an Indian engineering college and is a satire about the social pressures under an Indian education system.Farhan and Raju form a great bond with Rancho due to his refreshing outlook. Years later, a bet gives them a chance to look for their long-lost friend whose existence seems rather elusive.

0512 040834 Kirik Party (Comedy | Drama)
0512 040834 Kirik Party is the story of a gang of mischievous students, lead by the protagonist Karna, who has just joined an engineering college. Karna, the first-year engineering student, falls in love with Saanvi, a final-year pupil from his college. However, a tragic event changes his perception towards life and he mends his ways.

0212 043334 Forest Gump (Comedy | Drama)
0212 033334 Forrest, a man with low IQ, recounts the early years of his life when he found himself in the middle of key historical events. All he wants now is to be reunited with his childhood sweetheart, Jenny.

0212 071934 Father Soldier Son (Doccumentary | Military)
0212 071934 Father Soldier Son is a 2020 American documentary film directed and produced by Catrin Einhorn and Leslye Davis. It follows the family of Brian Eisch, a Sgt. First Class in the United States Army, and the effects of his deployment to the War in Afghanistan has on him and his young sons. When Sgt. First Class Brian Eisch is critically wounded in Afghanistan, it sets him and his sons on a journey of love, loss, redemption and legacy.

0112 093134 Aftershock (Tragedy|Family)
0112 093134 Tangshan, 1976. Two seven-year-old twins are buried under the rubble of the deadliest earthquake of the 20th century. The rescue team explains to their mother that freeing either child will almost certainly result in the death of the other. Forced to make the most difficult decision of her life, she finally chooses to save her son. Though left behind as dead, the little girl miraculously survives, unbeknownst to her brother and mother. AFTERSHOCK follows the family on their separate journeys over the course of the next 32 years, as they build lives forever shadowed by the traumatic experience of the earthquake, and eventually face each other--and the decisions of the past.
